Hello friends, I am Sagar and a
very warm welcome to all of you in today's
video. In today's video, we are going to talk
about the quarter 3 results of ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company. What kind of results and what
impact can be seen in the stock price.
First of all, if we talk, then
whatever results here,
we will try to talk by converting them from lakhs to crores.
Here, if we look at the total income of the company
which comes from premium, then the
total income
figure this time is seen to be
4362 crores, which was 400099 crores in the previous quarter.
If you are looking at the cotton quarters somewhere, then the premium is
seen to be declining,
but compared to the last year's December quarter, which
was 3854 crores last
year, the figure is seen to be increasing from there to 4300 crores. So,
if we are looking at the year 10 years, then
you can
see the premium increasing here, but let's
talk about the expenses here, what are the total expenses?  If it is seen happening then
this time the expense of 48 crores is
seen to be incurred by the company, if last year it was 3581 crores
then it is seen that the expense has increased from about 3500 crores to around 4
thousand crores
in the last quarter, if we
talk about 3988 crores, these almost 4000
crores were expense in the last quarter as well, so
this time the operating profit is seen to be
276 crores which
was 273 last year, so there is an increase of 3 crores, but if we
look at cotton, there is a big decline here
because the profit of 510 crores which was made by the
company at the operating level
in the September quarter and after tax, if
friends, we try to see the results this time, then the
figure that comes out this time is
seen to be almost
350 crores of profit after tax i.e.
352 crores, which is the figure that comes this time,
which was 590 crores last time, the
requirement of ₹590 in the last September quarter is almost half.  It is
visible that the
profit is falling by almost 45% quarter on quarter.
If we compare it with 10 years, then it has
increased from Rs 317 crore to Rs 352 crore, so it is falling quarter on
quarter, but the
increase of around 10%, i.e. 8 to 10%, is
visible here.
In this quarter, the company has given an inter-dividend of
Rs 450, so you will see an interest of Rs 450 here.
Also, if we talk about the IPS of this company, then
in this quarter you are
seeing Rs 718 paise, which was
Rs 12.3 paise in the previous quarter. So, there is
a big hit in the IPS, that is visible.
If we compare it with the last quarter of last year, then the
company had clocked an ups of around 6.5 here, but now we will
talk about what kind of face is visible in the chart, so the
stock of ICICI Lombard  You
can see on the chart on your screen that the
stock closed at ₹1250 today.
This stock appears to be trading lower above the 200-day moving average line.
However, if
you look at the entire month of December, the
stock appeared to be consolidating within a very small range. The
1280 level and the 1220 level
formed a good range on the lower side.
If you look at the last one and a half months of this stock, this range will
appear to be reducing the stock's losses and providing support.
If the stock
tries to go above 1280 or 1285, then
a rally may be seen in this stock. However,
if the stock
tries to break the 1220 or 1225 level due to a downward trend, then
you may see continued
selling pressure here,
and a significant
decline may also be seen.  The
levels up to Rs 1160-1180 can also be seen, then
you can see a downward movement, so
now we have to see what kind of
expectation is there after the results, what kind of upward or downward trend will be there
tomorrow, although the
market was already anticipating some weakness in the results,
but now we have to see
whether these results are really a deviation from the expectations
or the market will take it in a positive
way that the results here can be positive
in the coming quarters and a
positive impact of this will be seen, so
friends, I hope
you liked the video, if you like the video then do like,
share and subscribe to the channel, I will
meet you in my next video, till then
goodbye, thank you.